Yeah I. Just refused. To listen to
New Zealand. Law
or.
The or
a or Alberta early in the
early or.
Early early.
Early.
In the cell door opened that's all there
stood them escape in my view it's all very
irregular it might until the most
embarrassing repercussions expects Obama
certainly it's the responsibility of the
first magnitude I'm sorry Mr Wilson but
you left last all this discussion for
good away from sick alleged hacking the
repercussions of the responsibility if I
feel I'm responsible leave the cell door
open let him escape let him it's our only
chance I'm never one of them threaten me
with the bottom pits of hell and still I
insist this obscenity must be destroyed
you hear me to start.
A world.
Although brought by the head of F.E.M.A.
About all refasten just ready to
disembark. And traveling from my
hands then got
a list office but no help to.
Get your passports ready. In
infamy.
I managed to poison him
and. I don't want. To
Piss in this condition you know I'm killing
my husband. Not only isn't even the.
Second one I ask you. Think that institution
is your business in this condition you
have been for me. How. I
am travelling for my help.
You out
a lucky woman what comes
to. Follow. But money
makes pleas for the killers
there's the pacing of.
It But you know if you don't
get the waiting in time.
But then I can ask if this
is the fate of those.
And I'll. Yes. You have
lost I'm sure you know
what he's going my wife has found on him
he's gone to the photographers probably to
get
a new passport and new
instructions. And I wish
you know the very about some
friends scandal. Getting.
There is not such good frank
interest and cremated the truck.
Pulling. AHEAD AND MESSAGE
FOR friends can come.
From the all heist. Is forbidden I
command you in the name O.
Check out how to get.
To know just. The name he is using.
You could. In the United
States. The town of half.
The.
Yeah and that's it all the time to
get it over with so Saturday if you.
Don't have enough away tonight and I had
so many places you'd actually do it I had
to find a place to have a nice trip
to the capital has I get. Quite
a story I have here Mr. Potter is actually
excellent we care about everything years
old and. Like.
Water it's about. Half of that there is
a room there it's up to only one
it she was if you educate him
a head usually I'll.
Take issue with. This case I
put it here in this bag on
a target I don't even know responsibility
I just put it to punish the be there when
you want it I have. My bottom line and be
good and leave behind distribute How was
the best hotel in town. Best friends did
that mesh Peabody just just down the road
here peacefully. And.
This way mistreated Yes thank you.
Chad.
It's.
I.
Am. I am.
I make I mean. Yes it.
Is this is shows
a Bentley. Here. Yes he does but
he isn't here I don't expect. Yes
a few minutes or so. Hello. A few minutes.
I made. I mean
a week later. Yes if you like.
To. Thank you. Your
friend Mr Record. Your friend I met
a long string of you do what you.
Are trying to not to be here now. Sometimes
he stays after his last class but now
becoming straight here today are sure.
This is our wedding day we are getting
married yes but it's close. I know it's
most unconventional my being here today but
I want to get this great is that.
When he comes which way does he
come. From Webster hope it's the
big don't know the right over there you
see. The. Pollution I said it was.
All.
Right. It's
a friend. And it must be talking together
correct the church and the words into the
words here just. For the
press. And make sure.
Oh but that's all right going to go Oh man
are you off to Paperchase office chair I
go I don't like the trial you want
to have Jerry's job Mr Rankin take
a little off that way so I got to go with
us Mr Rankin or children or you want me.
Oh my lord I. Want to hire I'd
like to time greater things to
attend to will join us later we'll be out
till dark. I will catch up with you.
I'm.
My nephew Yes my Nicky. I
said what I had been telling.
The others but not tonight and then I
couldn't stand face to face with you friends
. You know much changed.
To back in your uniform.
You're very much the same sense I'm
a different man than before. Right
you. Too I'm different comrade and I.
You know I gathered you destroyed every
single item in Germany and Poland that
might have served as
a clue to my identity Well guess what
I'll be doing at six o'clock tonight.
Standing before a minister
of the gospel with
a woman's hand in mine the daughter of
a justice of the United
States Supreme Court
a famous liberal the girls even good to
look at yesterday camouflage is pretty.
Good thing two of the notorious friends
can do it in the sacred precincts of the
hop
a school surrounded by the sons of America's
First Families. And our state could.
Go into
a family strike again. It's.
Been really another war. What
is happening he should say for it just to
tell you this the family here he said to
be free that I said you can return to
your post and you are free. Behind just.
You know me and God.
I mean you managed inside of you. Religious
friends friends all those were open
to me all divorced. It's
possible that spirit.
They for ages so you leave them to me.
Have you been found out. If I was
here yes so far as you're. The one. He's
a pack any other man must trust
backing you had the man even smoked
a pack that had it coming
back for you discuss
a chilly. Action someone had down.
That's will be tough.
You killed a man with
a pact. The man apologise.
You no one else Bellagio.
Who must be brought to stone patient
friends. Confess your sins says I have.
Proclaimed your. Under duster
kind of thing something.
He really thinks of it will take strength
such pranks can come only from God.
Meal by the friends and together that
will pray to Him to give you strength.
I have sinned against heaven and before
these. I did not wish to be called
back on. It it was said to me. I can stare
at my feet. I despair of my sins.
On god of all goodness.
Calcutta ever to have
a fantasy about goodness.
Louise. All of.
The and in
the know
in the. In the early eighty's.
In or earlier in the world.
To. Earlier the early.
Early or. The.
That but.
Dearly beloved we are gathered together
here in the sight of God and in the face of
this company to join together this man
and this woman in holy matrimony.
And forsaking all others keep the only
unto her so long as we both shall live.
No acronym. Way yet
Jenny long for
a starter. Souping court
jesters you know. Bottle of
aspirin plays right back there sir just
down from the top you see the big winge on
the left and kind of excited you. Have
to get yourself Mr Right back there.
All of your needs are on our show just
look around help yourself. Right in there
right just one that says that shit that
shit that image speed but it. Just killed
a whole nation. That's probably too
late. Why should I get myself.
Tracked down cherish. Next
next three dollars even dive.
Down with claims that all the
people around here take it back.
On the right thank you. It was
largely my right the teachers
on the school change I. Oh yes I'm down.
It's. A. Challenge. Alright.
CLERK I have to protect now must be quite
a responsibility photons are running
down you might say. We usually make it
fair and. We offer. Twenty
five cents to game.
Stephanie but I'll take
a flyer make many of those and. Go.
All right. Now you must know just about
everybody in town here not just about
now everybody has their own visions.
Now. Challenge something. Don't.
Buy. Or antique dealer.
Judge Longstreet got the best flexion
these parts do you no good now I don't
suppose you sell. In
the know there are any
other out of town by. I think I would
prefer to commit this morning.
Team on the same bus with you. Acute
case here never did come back for.
He might have been one. He
was more the missionary.
But you here but man just look in the phone
book time in the ferry where I sit and
finish and I'm fortunate looking.
Actually said Mr. Medlock serious.
Catch to bed.
Again we get to keep in mind
on. Twenty five centuries.
I mean I won't pretend I'm not disappointed
so far that has anybody seen my brand
new husband in turn tell me he deserted
you already it's like this the proof of
this is reading these things out. That legal
finding for me the one point one five
cats hurry up.
I've looked everywhere for him and I can't
find him one of way could be I'm getting
Why are you doubting
what about. To change.
I should like you better.
Drop this post be going on
a honeymoon essentially. Give me five in.
The.
World.
Oh. That you're working out there
a lot. I was getting
around your typical thing.
My name was on Long Street
No no you. Couldn't judge in
a two way lot front but I actually it was
like sixteenth century probably by brick
to prosper. The clock. I wouldn't
know my brother was going to work.
No no no he's on his honeymoon he plans to
work out I want to get back oh is he an
expert Well yes but it's really more of
a hobby with him really. Just
with me too. He's has to be
back on Friday because examinations.
He's one of the teachers at school.
I name is rank and.
It's nice to be able to show it to someone
I don't know. But personally it is my
specialty is truth. To that. The. Ship
although sometimes heavy and design
almost invariably. Shows they sign
a message that's when it's
beautiful. No. Matter and yeah
you might also matter HOW DO YOU WANT TO
DO A child wreck I do how do you do if you
don't mind my intruding on your homecoming
getting married. Yes How are you mind
you looking good to me Well Miss may
have had already. If you know send down
to get a call is coming out on
a day and. Not all of them
out. I'm going to tell you
what you have how you're not right just
your usual place got it all right. Yet if
you count them as though you walk up and
down and you want to kiss you on that very
topic beginning to remember to keep your
name together apparatus and. Listen
here's competitive catalog before revealing
how my Mr Wilson is also an authority
on clocks Oh really the style of having
him Yes So your brother tells me I'm
standing on
a fixed one in the church though I may try
well that's quite an undertaking show
the kind of
a life I am I hope the sales like happy
just the way it is even if the clock
doesn't run. We've been
hopping last. Since
Friday we go. You lost the day I pass you
up on Friday by the way how's the head
oh that much improved thanks to you doctor
you were heard on Thursday remember the
day of the wedding. Yes that's
right. Wednesday I left Bangor and.
We were hurting to worsen over nothing
serious. While serious enough to raise
a bump on his head the size of
a billiard ball the usual dog. Thing you
know that sister that dog also being so
noble. But all right red white and he is
from to see me and. To think like I was
your meeting at
a. Meeting foreign policy decision I
read the fellows report Standish and.
He's full of proof Well that's the way
they used to talk in the one nine hundred
thirty S. No of Standish
the London Times man
a brilliant use of course use quoting
rumors mostly men driving by night you know
underground meeting places pagan rituals
do you believe. On anything's possible.
I'm sorry sir but I think it's ridiculous
for them maybe some fanatics but no
German is right mind can still have
a taste for war. You know
what Germany was drank and.
I'm sorry I. Have
a way of making enemies and subject
pretty unpopular where we should consider
it the objective opinion of an
objective historian historian.
Sekai actually could explain it better
the German sees him self as the innocent
victim of world envy and hatred spite against
set upon by inferior peoples inferior
Nations he can admit to where
a much less to wrong doing about the German
we chose to ignore Ethiopian Spain but
we learned from our casualty list the
price of looking the other way when
a truth everywhere I've come to know for
whom the bell told the German. He still
follows his warrior gods. Marching of our
canary and strange his eyes still fixed
upon the fire is the secret and in those
separating meeting places that you don't
believe in the germans dream world comes
alive and he takes his place in shining
armor beneath the balance of the Teutonic
Knights mankind is waiting for the
Messiah but for the German. The Messiah
is not the Prince of Peace. He's.
Another barbarous. Another Hitler.
Well then you you have no faith in the
reforms that are being affected in Germany.
Cried Oh no Mr Wilson I can't believe
that people can be reformed except from
within the basic principles of equality and
freedom never have never will take root
in Germany the will to freedom has been
voiced in every other town all men are
created equal leave it
a Gallatin Tennessee but. In German marks
proletarians United who have nothing to
lose but your chains remarks from the
German my sister to my dear child if we
concede your argument there is no solution.
For once again I differ. What is that
and. Annihilation. Of
the last bit in these.
Chats I can't imagine you advocating
and Kathy Chaney and peace. For it was
a story that was to Marge of the world
doesn't have much trouble for crises in the
past two thousand years.
Speaks up pedagogue.
Speaking it teaches most of us and clear
the faculty is coming for tea next Tuesday
if you have nothing better to do would you
like to join. I'd like to but my work
here is finished. I'm leaving topic more.
Extraordinary isn't it clasping Mr Wilson's
hobby to their business already how do
you know how. Can I rather think I thank
you for whatever I got immunity not just
that if you. Need the work I'm restless.
I'll be in Washington tomorrow at noon
you are right about rank and. Is above
suspicion. Are.
There any. Red. Herring.
Again. I mean not just as.
I Washington D.C.
.
But
a Nazi would deny that Karl
Marx because he was evil. I
think I'll stick around for
a while. But
if you. Handed it to me.
That little man. Pardon me.
I do not care I told you about it. He
came here the day we were married.
Quite
a secret I mean. I had never had
a game like that before.
The track and. Thanks.
To the new man was. Walking
all by himself. Across
a deserted city square. Where
every mood is rushed out.
But when he moved away to us. The Shadow
stayed there behind him and spread out
just like
a carpet. We should think
we might have been over
to. Try to get.
It to happen.
Fisher get
a good lease part pretty fair like double
up right I've got the wrong clothes on
but they probably want
mine to thank you but.
I'm lucky to do this on. SO I CAN YOU are
right I don't mind if I do thank you for
. All your folks like fishing all my
dad's great your drink this stuff and.
What about Charles Charles. All. I
have to call him is to write to school
a little mixed up some stuff. He spends
most of time on the clock you know.
Why don't you like him now. What do you
mean you don't like your brother in law.
It's not my business but I wish you'd
tell me why well I like him well
enough. Alone is reason why should YOU DON'T
TELL ME I'M But again because I know I
appetite can't help myself. It's
my business. I hate bringing you
into this no I but you're the only one I
can tell I do I need you help very badly.
With. The system may be in great trouble
I know that you're man enough what I'm
going to ask you to do for the
truth is I'm not really and.
I'm sort of
a detective. What you want me to do
Mr Wilson. It would help me
a lot if I knew every move Charles Rankin
made on the day of his wedding right up
to the ceremony Well I should be able to.
Unless Charles realizes what I'm doing
I'll keep him busy.
Gee Mr Wilson you must be wrong Mary
wouldn't fall in love with that kind of
a man I hope I am wrong no but I
have to way it is people can't help
who they voted.
By Mr WEST. In.
A fashion.
Here you have
a festering wound to fix stuff. On
. Figured your time right.
And will be certain round
a better friend. Than
a man or woman and you
Mr Wilson. I don't know.
I could not make much of
difference much danger as. Well.
As my folks twenty five cents you know.
By the way that was to rank and pick up
a supper this evening. Each out
against you up there Mark. Now.
You know. It's knackered
me these need.
A middle man ever that pick up
a suitcase that is so strange
to. Have been tempted once or
twice to the pretty much insanity.
Seems to mean that under
circumstances that you have a perfect right
to do. That I would want to do it not
a witness against me. And so on we're
going to drown in that so you can see.
What I want to know. So
I let him. Whatever.
Soak in the Razor. Our way there's this
Christabel process. Where all sure
yeah yeah. I think that religious
family Yeah actually all.
I think about. A little sooner you
are three. Mr Potter and I have been
poking our notice in the somebody else's
business that. Kept read that you know me
never did call back. It's been more two
weeks ago they say what I was doing I have
no look in the phone book didn't telephone
kind of funny looking he was scrawny
little brother with big stary blew up we
walk back every second it might break into
a brick. Did he have
a foreign accent or yes he did. Not see
much of an accent is there and we're
talking you have no no he could
be missing right and. Why I know.
I was just trying to compete
a mystery for you. Don't all foreign
strangers have to have fun X.X.
. Mary have you seen red I know not
since I do honey
a couple of days ago spending all his time
on the woods and I didn't come home for
his meal but you told me never ran away you
never did that's why I know so anxious
for
a moment. Good night as to
us right now on night. We're
able to find out anything. That he did
go to rockets. And your sister did
see him. Did Mary say so she
started to. My sister is
a fine woman no but she must find that
kind of man. You don't know Mary she
she wouldn't listen to anything against
much less believe no we must arrange it so
that she finds out her so.
You understand. One thing
certain she knows nothing now nothing at
all except that he didn't want to admit
having Seems I want you to say. I'd give
something to know what explanation is
making right now it was a student
engineered that. There was
a girl. That died before I was
to leave I went out on the lake.
She told me and I sacrificed an area she'd
never intend to show. I thought she was
joking. Ass remember. She wasn't.
Sure I could stop her she
stood up in the boat.
Like. I dived in after it was too late
she was gone only one person and we
were on the lake together the brother. He
knew I hadn't heard it but he told me he
wanted to call it an accident four cops
should. Give him I hadn't of Switzerland.
As the years went by I would myself
to believe that that it was to. Be.
On our wedding day marry
if you're sick and.
I gave him all the money I have
in the world. Right away again.
You should have told me. Carry this.
Awful thing around by yourself.
For three hours. And. You.
Have. To go that Christmas. Well.
I suppose when you see
any money going to for
a better. Darling I'm terribly nervous and
I'll work up the clock and hope tonight
them or so will come. Do you want
to stand Champ Car scientists.
So I was. You. Know do this to me.
Pretty like they had to all right and
how but there's nothing to be free.
You heard my whistle. You can bark
or anything. Just crawl this far.
Why do you think you dime
Let's go on time down.
That young street dog red it's like he's
dead to me they take him back to Dr large
office but you know any better.
For We're actually many many.
Checkers. You know. Coaching little.
Thanks for strength.
For a log of the dog live with. More than
a minute or so. Must
have been placed within
a few hundred yards. And the
latter part of the distance.
Must have been moving slower
and slower. Thank you
very much. Thanks. Michelle.
Did you visit that
magazine Mike is very
a classic. Bad. Acting
but. After you know it
bring him right in there.
Is a law say about this kind of
murder is the same as killing
a man. It ought to be just
as bad. For pause Monday.
No mud on hind. Reilly's
makes for the much.
Read my spending somewhere in the
woods of any idea what for Mr Wells.
The body I think. Mine in case the little.
Just party thing wrong wrong wrong
being good enough I've just gone on
a search but you have to have
a machine know what to search for the body
state police kept eyes half the town if
we kept there for show
one misses and here is
a crack to our. Side of the searching for
my British credibility back here strong
a little ducks. Back a
look and I knew it come to
a bad end at RB fifteen cents best
dressed how to put down your town.
Oh Sara tell me you're up here. All right
Becky I'm going somewhere we aren't
dearest I am. And you talking about as
a rule men leave their wives because they
don't love them but. I must leave you
because I do or you want object once you
know the kind of man you've married.
That you are the man I married and that's
all that matters. Doubting I meant it
when I said for better or for
worse. Even to. The killing really.
Couldn't. It was an accident
so I meant to kill it. Murder can be
a chain everyone makes leading to another
to it so if you make. Bread was taking up
the grave. Of the man I
killed. Yes your little man.
Should kill. The Beast and.
The same and sort of hold
you close to me Are you satisfied to
let me go. Because. Why should you do
it I don't give in my head but his dreams
were grand doing you know the true father
was doing he was the justice Longstreet
would be glad to protect his daughter from
any scandal the right thing
a few facts about. Mary I. Should
have gone away and lost myself in
a world where you can never
find me but. I loved you. Was
weak. To him. It's one of his
goes we thought. He would if he had
half my trouble fight having me.
Charles. What is the.
Last thing you know. You. Knew
him. And you need have no fear
if I'm the only one who
can speak Mary. You
become going to. But I'm
already in part. Because I'm
a part of you. That you
shot at the first touch of
the Dutchman to. Close your eyes
off. To be batting back
down with the sheriff looking up the coroner's
office while it was the same for her
for she's changed at the very
near. Even Mr Gresham even
or even just by mistake.
So we do about. Leave her
alone with him though we know. She realizes
now that whatever story he told her
about my ticket was
lost. You know. I think
your sister should be ready
to you the truth. Child.
With
a name to get the ball. Because
I couldn't do it. I mean I don't
think I could. Stand Paris in
a dead person. I.
Really are going to marry twenty eight
all together he didn't need. Me or
twenty eight just you. You
know how we manage I.
Suppose that you should quote I don't know
I mean I'm terrified of seeing anybody
or things married. Ask
a title if you're. Going to turn to go
through this thing is to go for an executive
producer who talked just
a few stories. To
go to the police and others there he wants
to talk to you yes thank you say oh.
Yes I think so. Just
a minute now see. He wants me
to come over. He asked me to.
Say he wanted to see me alone.
It's nothing unusual about
a father wanting to see his
daughter is that. Is there no.
All right out of my right
over. To think I struck
the street which strange not strange. Tell
you what I'll do I'll go to the church
and work out
a car for you with your father and you
can buy and pick me up later. But
it is what you think. Christiane is so
different you know what you're going to
certainly.
Coming there. Is something around.
You know about the body that was discovered
yesterday I was writing. Yes. It drove
me to deceive. No no no I never
met him I would see in the body
well. Well then. How can you
be sure you never meant it.
Because I can't be certain. Mr Moss and
you suspect me of something if so what
a feeling of murder of. Perhaps this
photograph will be fresher memory. If you
recognize this man. That is Conrad Meineke
commander in charge of one of the more
efficient concentration camps. You know him
don't you. You haven't met him here and
Hopper. No no I've never
seen that night Mr Wilson.
Judge would you mind putting out
the lights. I've been showing
a father should tell me and I'd like
you to see them too. I'm on the Allied
commission for the punishment of war
criminals. It's my job to bring escape not use
to justice. It was the job
that brought me to hop but.
Surely you don't think it. Was not never
had never so much as even seen and well
you might without you realizing that it
looked like other people and act like other
people want to share their
benefit. Gas Chamber
Mr Frank and. The candidates were first
given hot showers so that their laws would
be open and gas would act that
much more quickly. And this is
a line to. Which hundreds of men women
and children were buried alive.
And if you want me to look at these
horrors all this you're seeing.
It's all a product of
one mind. The mind of
a man named. Francis Kindler.
France Canada you know he was the
most brilliant of the gang of minds of the
Nazi party. You just can't conceive the
theory of genocide matched the population
of conquered countries so that regardless
of who won the war Germany would emerge
the strongest nation in Western Europe
biologically speaking unlike gave
both him and the rest of them. I had
a passion for anonymity the newspapers
carried no picture of him oh no and just
before he disappeared to be destroyed every
evidence that might link him with this
passed down to the last fingerprint
there's no clue to the identity of French
Canada except one wouldn't think. He
has a hobby that almost amounts to
a mania clock. So if lots of people.
You yourself might lie I'm not quite
finished Mrs Rankin. In prison
in Czechoslovakia war criminal was awaiting
execution this was Conrad money one
time executive officer for French contract.
He was an obscenity on the face of the
year. Stench or burning flesh. But we
gave him his freedom on the chance
that you might believe me to. Eat
at medium striken. And here I lost.
Until yesterday. Good Dog great fun for me
but unfortunately my Nicky was dead and
buried. Now in all the wood.
There's only one person who
can identify friend skinned.
That person is the one no no. No
definitely would mind if
you came to Hopper to see.
Now it's. My cows and not at. You want to
rock and stuff during the afternoon of the
day that are where I can see out that
anyone come by you when I am going to not
try hard to remember it's not so long ago
and two weeks we were hanging curtains
knowing where you're going all the time. You
know who else was there. He came right
after his last past. And we were
together for one thing people who are nothing
like my cousin with this man came to
accept it whilst Christian it's
a ridiculous fish trying to use me to
implicate him and you can't you can't involve
me in a lie that's told is
a lie. To hide from it's
not. Every marriage. When
it's matter.
Of minutes or stuff.
You know that your words there are no
arranged more to me than anything to you. Yes
you have. To face this thing with
complete honesty just to. Your entire
happiness may well depend on your
telling me the absolute. Worst in is
right. Innocent the matter Diprivan. And
it is no matter there's no call upon your
lawyer to do what. He's good.
He's good he wouldn't hurt any
anybody except to protect somebody
you love to see. A true friend.
Charles was not with you that afternoon
she. Again you didn't go out and
yes you are. You don't even.
Really need.
She has
a fax now. She won't accept.
To hobble for had to
acknowledge. Not so much that right can
be kinda low but that she could ever have
given our love to such
a creature. But we have one
out. Of step countries.
It knows what the truth is struggling to
be heard. The will to troops within your
daughter is much too strong to be denied.
If you don't charge Rankin we should
be able to expose him without too much
difficulty I'm not interested in proving
that he isn't Charles right I'm only
interested in proving that he's friends kinda
like how do you propose to do that. For
your daughter. Unless I'm
mistaken she's headed for
a breakdown that's usually responsible
person being able to divided reckon we're
recognized and that's what I'm
banking on. Cab for to trust
a person approaching you still he won't be
left to act he may try to escape before
she collapses which would only be an
admission of guilt. All. Go on you make
him
a. Shock cold bloodedness.
Natural the problem. Because
you are
a long story that I'm talking to you about
this. Naturally you try to pretend that
it means. However the proof that murder is
a would be the strongest evidence
that your daughter could.
Less stress for. You to scratch out just
like you say Mr must because there you try
to tell me that you're in that city.
To make that connection you know being
a skating that really makes it
a clever that will spur his idea was to
start by me and telling him about the man.
Wanted to say so I was.
Transgender. And he made it
all of just
a trick and I didn't tell him anything and
I didn't tell father I think how they
spoke of. It was simple enough to prove
you're not. Just find somebody who is in
your class at college and you identify you
know that's all they'll be doing. Right
. But I want to I promise
I won't even touch an
automatic day. Challenge we.
Just couldn't agree. Mr. Smiley
to understand that you are
right.
And we should have got
a jewish dad module and it was just to be
home professors sure knock it off my ass
off to graduation Mr Right that was the
right way to do what I want to know is
going to chime or not go on how do you
but again you just need to face. All of.
Them tripping the jury is going to be are
not loose they were fifteen minutes up
that will happen. So I've told you I was.
These curtains drawn I don't like the
sunlight streaming in a bad for them Mary
that's rubbish you know that they have
a house we have
a proof that they don't know you are my
house and I want them. To suit yourself
that. It's going to be good
for the party. It's that time
already.
Were you able to see when they opened the
grave Mr Randall if you are really where
I'm not the most pleasant sight I think
Mary had down there you. Will not remain
that's where there's been this I think it
was actually rather. Back in one ranch
we don't approve of. Manufacturing least
raising good and plenty of luck started
bombing every time believe Mrs Rand
ordered some ice cream to ice cream here
already gone there's a
book for our show to give
a joy. To watch. From
a stranger would be setting foot outside
the house and let's find her alive who is
he was. The murderer I mean weaving for
a new victim. I hope you have got to you
were kind enough to invite the receiver.
Of course no use to us just thought recipe
for the ice cream good sirs waiting for
it I hope it has melted.
And I want to tell you
a lot I guess I would drink for you all
just where this neither you nor doctor are
pretty old yes of course well I just can't
use you. But I'm going to get you some
careful stepping Hood
a taste and we're going to believe that
it was always Dr Ro good oh he'll be here
in just
a few months I want everyone to their
mother probably have put it out there who
mother and you have traditionally been to
the three weeks ago yes I'm answering the
look you have now got you
so I don't know just
a guy and Jeff if I know what was that
French Mistake ahead. Yes. If I may well
be generous doesn't waste all day in the
war to my palace I think Sheldon that is
to be just three weeks ago and there will
be much more Thank you know. People.
Gently I guess you know we remember what
Emerson says about crying over those red
ink and he may know I to be laid.
Off Oh hello there I can buy
you know the quotation and listen for
tales I'm crying on the earth is made of
glass and I don't. Commit
a crime in the US is made to.
Commit crimes. Committed
crimes. And it seems as if
a coat of snow fell on the ground such as
reveals in the woods the track of every
population fox squirrels mole You
cannot recall the spoken word you
cannot wipe out for track you cannot drop
the letters so as to leave no clue you
know Mr Wilson on ship do you know your
number one suspect and on that I can call
him so far you know the only suspect
possible to degrade you he thinks you
committed the crime to get possession of
the price that they. Need to make it out
with you the proper nouns probably the
knife that make you study Bank of. America
that's worse than doing it I don't. Get
invited on the show for the after i don't
know. Your eyes just kind of right.
I got it right nice but.
No no.
Mariano Rivera
a. Little ride to school. It
broke in the bean spilled
all over the floor.
When I left that it's still here
a dry place not capable.
Sub conscious of like one.
Now on it was the way we moved it was Frank
makes. He's never to leave the house
unless I know where she's going. For any
reason I can be found she's to be detained
a matter of what the text. Does but you
get behind. Just know those beaches
signed all deformed when getting back
you know hands. Every time she walks
on
a separate sidewalk. Is Near something that
can fall drives an automobile anything
that would result in an accidental death.
And life is in danger if she won't get
behind me.
Was.
Good afternoon gentlemen. Of the day we
will attempt to finish with the career of
three to the girl Sarah clinic from Royston
course from Brandenburg Prince phone
call of. Frederick the Great to you.
Kate sixty eight so you can beat
a sense. Oh
Mary. Sure. Can you I
mean you. Can speak for an hour before
him but I want you to understand this.
Something very important to come up. You
must come to the church immediately. The
church tower anything. Just stand I don't
want anybody to know that you're going.
I don't tell anybody you're going go to
the church door and leave your car in the
rear and come into the back room.
I. Got
a. Check for the rest get back to
work for us.
Watch that Mr Peabody.
Gone someplace. With
you. When I asked you what he
was going to marry I heard. So
you seem to forget I'm
no longer a child and
a married man when you ain't
been married do you know. Mrs
Rankin. What is it I'm going to her if
you don't need to go buy my head off.
What is it. Well I. If you've got
something to say say it what is
a terrorist. A lady indeed I don't
mean to be like if I could be
a lot of hair maybe not so I'm. Not
a does I have to be. The most dramatic
stuff but he does not tell you.
That I didn't do that. So there I'm
sorry but I pretty sure the feeling
is I didn't mean to really I didn't. Sarah.
Now I couldn't get along without you
and you know that don't you. But don't
you. Know you honestly honestly said I
wasn't. It fair Sara please we don't mean.
Sarah you will never leave me with you know
how I feel about your daughter yes I do
like it was my own daughter you might
wonder how could I so I've got to go now
really I do I promise to be
somewhere but where do you miss me.
Stop pursing Sarah. It's
a secret. That's
not in. My heart what I think I
get really. Oh no let me just
let me in the. Right there he.
Knows maybe I don't you're not
I hear you know it. Was me if I
want to use one trail please.
I look I'm supposed to meet Charles at the
clock tower and right away and I can't
get there when you go and tell him to
please wait for me. And though I don't want
to know where or why you're
going at it it's important.
To three. Well we're speaking Mr Wilson.
Barrett coming up right now.
Oh this is right and this is not
a stone is that after all as you ladies
are working too hard it's like every
convention we close this huge military
city you're perfectly right I dismissed
class ten minutes early.
Right three forty four.
Strike check is a must
a part of it I didn't feel I. Do you know
what you are missing Meghan you're the
added One of the yesterday.
Not.
Sure I'd like to date I am sure you know
it but I have to Mr Phillips are right
that I know I'm here but it's run away by
the middle of all this part of it but I
don't read back to Bill. Bennett whatever
that box for children to watch the whole
thing out. How much do you want eighty
five cents an awful lot of the kumite.
You want to spank rocky but
you know that's probably
a bad influence. I don't is that
a compliment you may depend on I don't
know about it. I'd like to get even. Your
most. You really have to wind up if you
still smell
a clue why you joined. The peer pressure
I could do it coming up for snow.
Because your professor.
Never met.
Charles.
He didn't go to church No no says error
about zero just as I was leaving soon I had
some kind of an attack she's resting
how he's just that it wasn't
a serious but that I should stay with.
What's the matter. And why did
you have to go to the church.
Who said it was important. Is important
I think. It's my sense of fortunate.
For its. Peace Trust what is.
I'm sorry. I just began to feel
a strain you see I have my
Wheatley's to. Tell you
of my own. They found out anything more
honest than this one for I know you don't
want to see anybody all they
have been in that room is
a rumor going around that this unrest
with me. In sort of the beach yesterday.
Made me doubt your strength maybe going
too far then told you something. Head.
You didn't have to be. And you tell no.
More about. The same question. Which is you
coming directly from the church and my
being cross-examined Tom knowing but when
I found I couldn't leave Sarah I called
no one told him to go there and tell you I
was just being I told her not to call me
but it was surely no time to try not to go
hi can I talk to my friend is going to.
Be dicey is probably on your hands you're
a man living in the midst. Of an
argument you. Know that you need to be.
On that day. To tell no
not yes if he does the
tragic times I think that there. Are
as I intended to kill him to
know why I did I. Scanned.
Kill. Only I want you to I could thank my
God what I've been doing you want but I
want to know what it's. Like when you
kill me don't want to talk to me.
Just
a. Merry
. ON
THE INSIDE AFRICA
a cop read it get me the USA placed. Yes
The roadblocks are up. We're watching the
railroad station and he's been hiding in
the perch. One hundred.
Thousand nine. Hundred.
And. Man.
Nine hundred.
S.
. Just
go to the village.
And.
Mr WILSON Well if he is what I think he is
it's going to be they will do everything
possible to bring him back to the Mr
Will. Not in the House not to ask.
Him off with that's what he's hiding
she gets credit for us. All we
do. Talk after seven years in the
deputies get all the help you can where.
The church the church the pope you.
A url A.
Dope. I have
a gun. You don't need it.
I'm in them. Are you doing.
This me up.
You're telling the truth.
Why should I lie. To
a father here I came by all the way
to the cemetery no one Sunday.
I needed the excuse I was afraid
you would let me ask. What you
are came to.
No married few of us got
a day. To remember through that. You're
going to. End up lying
if I take you with me.
You are. And search the words watch them
like God looking into the last part
of the words don't search there again
a day or two of the show I got up to make
fine maybe I'll know you are still here
but they're having a virgin breakdown
you've cracked. My eyes would you be
a big. Time to come to church to do
tonight. The child could see you going to
killing you soon coming is what led you
here. And you want to know if you're now.
Let out I know not. Rest but
that all practice to us in
a very forthright direction shall you
know wish. I don't need any tricks no
matter what happens to me tricks won't
do you any good. You often finish half
French and. Act. I.
Citizens or papa. That come after
you complain to the Lord never
a people who want you been laughing at
a French scandalous letter you can't
afford them any more will show you kill me
a marriage happen people down that there's
no escape. You know that would explode
and I knew it was only half that closing
in on you when there was only this room
and this room to Bush closing in on you.
Two of the things they say they did so
that I did not order you gave
the. I don't make it my duty.
To see. The I'm not
a criminal you're. A
little.
The in
a just. A
lot. A lot.
Earlier.
The the.
Yeah.
The new.
All right the N.R.A.
They want to get us down out of the no
thanks I want to be heated and I. Don't get
to come on down or not I'm
not a good man you let out
a bad my uncle busted my ass coming from
here all the way to my friends I'm taking
it easy.